The Metal Breath Gets Stolen
The Metal Breath?
The Metal Breath is a legendary treasure from planet Machina.
I simply refuse to believe it would end up on such a minor planet...
Me see it clearly!
Child's bracelet smelled like mighty Deus Machina!
I saw with my own eye too, Buster Gallon!
That little earthling was commanding the Star Guardian like one of his lackeys!
Black Hook, what I want to know is-
Call me Captain.
Ah, uh... C-Captain.
What is it, Buster Gallon?
Ahem. What I want to know is... what do you plan to do once you get your hands on the Metal Breath?
Hmm. Well, what would you do?
The one who holds the Metal Breath can rule over all Metal Cardbots.
I would use that power to conquer the entire universe!
Then we can divide it amongst us three, of course.
That sounds fun.
Yes. That much should be obvious.
But that child has Blue Cop, a Star Guardian by his side!
It will not be easy.
Is there any way around this?
Of course there is. You can leave it to me.
Mom! Where are the towels?!
I told you to take them when you went upstairs!
I'm busy cleaning! You come get them yourself!
Augh, Mom!
Ugh. Fine.
Ugh. He'll become spoiled if I keep this up.
I'll leave the towel here!
I love you, Mom!
Ugh. Save it.
Hmph.
Aaaiyah!
Aah! What kind of animals are these?!
Take that!
What's going on?
There's a bunch of strange mice out here!
Huh?
Here-
Uh... They must've ran downstairs!
Honey! Be careful of the mice!
What? Did you say mice, darling?
Ah, feeling fresh!
Oh, my Metal Breath!
...uh... Heavy Iron...
...sealing... gonna seal you...
Wha... where did it...
How did it get down there?
Aaah!
Stop right there!
W-what's going on out here?!
Waugh!
The Mini Gallons have succeeded in stealing the Metal Breath.
Although it took longer than expected.
Well done, Buster Gallon!
Heheh. Bring it back quick!
Hm? Good morning, Jun-
Give it back!
HOT!
Where are they hiding?
What's all the ruckus this morning?
Get back here!
Oh!
Sorry, Mom!
Oi oi! Who the heck are these guys?!
Gotcha!
Uh... Jun, what are you doing?
Did you forget that we were going to do our homework together?
That's not important right now! The Metal Breath has been st-
Huh? Where did they go?!
The Metal Breath...
Stop right there!
The Metal Breath was stolen?!
How did this happen? Who could have done this?
It was those little guys over there! They look like Black Hook's crewmate!
Juuuuun!!
I said stop!
Just a little more!
You almost got them, Jun!
Stop!
I got them!
Way to go Anna, you're the best!
I- wait a minute!-
Please stop it!
I can't hold them any longer!
Anna, are you alright?!
Ow... I'm really sorry, Jun...
It's okay, I think we've driven them in the right direction!
Luckily they're headed straight for Uncle Edo's car center!
Huh? They snuck inside here?
Yes! So please help me look for them too!
I really need your help, guys!
What a bunch of pesky little things. Even if they did come in here, it will take some time before we find...
...Them?
Why they just go round and round in circle?
Are they broken?
That's impossible!
Where are they?
A... car center just outside of Mowtown.
Me go check on them.
What are you going to do?!
Wait for me!
Hm... I've got a bad feeling about this.
You little rats!
Way to go!
Those little guys are pretty slippery!
Listen up, I have a plan.
Aha! I got it!
Metal Cardbot, setup!
Trying to steal all of us? I'll admit, you have some guts.
Yeah. They sure do.
Now whattaya say we show 'em some hospitality?
I agree. Should we make them tell us where we can find Black Hook's hideout?
They're getting away!
I've had enough running around...
Hand over tiny trio!
Huh...?
Buffalo Crush! Just barging in like that won't solve anything!
Huh?
My precious little mini-mes!!
How can this be?...
Uh, uh... I-I dunno.
Hey! If you're here to fight, then hurry it up!
Buffalo Crush! Let's retreat for now!
No retreat! Me not leaving without Jun and Metal Breath!
Yaaah!!
Buffalo Crush!
Me get revenge for tiny trio!
That was your fault!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Dexter, setup!
Dexter, Helix Sword!
Helix Sword!
Let's put a hole in those axes! Spear Thrust!
Hole?
Spear Thrust!
Step aside, Buffalo Crush!
Chest Cannon!
Buffalo Crush! We need to retreat!
Me can still fight!
Now is not the time!
You need to know when to call it quits, Buffalo Crush!
Black Hook!
I'll admit, today was a defeat for the Black Crew!
Black Crew?
B... Black Crew?
Me not your henchman! Me hate that name!
And you're not black! You're blue!
E-enough!
I told you to call me Captain!
-I'm staying out of this. This is getting embarassing.
-No! Put me down!
Ahem. Anyways! The legacy of Deus Machina will be mine!
Deus Machina's legacy?
If you mean the Metal Breath, that's a misunderstanding!
And why should I believe you?
Ah! All done.
Hey Wild Guardy, your sword is as good as-
Ahaha... thank goodness...!
Right? Yeah!
Hey, kids?
Uncle Edo!
Would you care to explain all this?
Uh, w-well...